It's usually the beat for 99.9% of the
time um and then it's the hook and then
it's like done once you have the hook
it's like done that's the hardest part
you know what I mean like but it's also
the easiest part cuz if it's hard then
like I just skip it that's why I have a
like I have a playlist on my computer of
just like thousands of Beats those are
all Beats that I love but it's like I
skipped them because it's like the hook
didn't instantly come so I was over it
once the hook comes I mean you just fill
it in with verses and then you're out I
don't like try to over complicate things
I just go out feeling watch my videos in
exclusive content on your TV or follow
at Music Choice
[Music]